Charles and Ray were a team. They were husband and wife.
Чарльз и Рэй были командой. Они были мужем и женой.
Despite the New York Times' and Vanity Fair's best efforts recently,
Несмотря на все недавние усилия журналов "Нью-Йорк Таймс" и "Ярмарка тщеславия"-
they're not brothers. (Laughter)
они не были братьями. (Смех)
And they were a lot of fun.
Они были очень весёлыми ребятами.
You know, Ray was the one who wore the ampersands in the family.
В их семье знак "&amp;" носила Рэй.
(Laughter)
(Смех)
We are going to focus on Charles today, because it is Charles' 100th birthday.
Сегодня в центре внимания будет Чарльз, потому что это его 100-летний юбилей.
But when I speak of him, I'm really speaking of both of them as a team.
Но, говоря о нём, я говорю о них двоих как о настоящей команде.
Here's Charles when he was three. So he would be 100 this June.
Вот Чарльз, когда ему было три года. В июнe ему бы исполнилось 100 лет.
We have a lot of cool celebrations that we're going to do.
Мы готовим множество классных мероприятий, чтобы это отпраздновать.
The thing about their work
Что касается их работы,
is that most people come to the door of furniture --
то большинство людей узнают о ней, открывая для себя их мебель:
I suspect you probably recognize this chair
подозреваю, вы наверняка узнаете этот стул,